My first live performance as a trainee.
Being under those spotlights felt like being wrapped in a warm blanket.
If I had disappeared right then and there, I honestly wouldn't have minded one little bit.
What is this? Where did they go? Chieri? Everyone!
Don't go!
Please! You can't leave me! Come back!
Kira, please shine for me! Shed some light on this darkness!
Karara isn't the only one who shines.
Achan...
You yourself must shine. Don't be afraid. Sing as long as your voice lasts. Sing and make your presence known.
Please!
Nagisa! Nagisa!
Let me guess. You stayed up all night and practiced?
Chieri?
Start by relaxing your shoulders and loosening your upper body.
Like this?
Two... relax and bam!
Oh! I don't have anything to go bam with!
Just keep practicing.
Ribbon!
Come out! Come out! Wherever you are!
Here it is!
Hold still, Sonaji. You know you really should learn to eat without making such a mess.
Darn! Too tight!
Hey! When I'm MCing, can I talk about how your chest has gotten bigger and drive the boys wild?
What? No! Why would you even think about that?
Lighten up! It's all a good bun!
Eyes forward, girls!
It's time to meet up.
Ready? It's time to show them the fruits of our labor.
Let's go!
Mm-hmm!
That's it! I'll sing out loud!
I'll sing out my presence!
I'll sing out that we're all members of AKB-0048!
Let's sing out loud!
JP-0048!
Rox-0048!
Cheers!
Once you sing out loud!
Charlestown, having to step on.
Let's sing out loud!
Be very low!
It's a lot more and candidly!
Open and over to join us for a better rappwl!
bugün, your chance for the real酷 ever!
球!
The big bidder!
Woohoo!
Hey, this one!
We're incognito, remember?
It's neat.
I never thought hiding in plain sight would be so thrilling!
You're as bold as ever, aren't you, Yuko?
It's so cool to see how we look from the audience perspective, you know?
It gives a whole new appreciation for what we're doing up there!
I think next time I'll come alone!
Oh no you don't! The last thing we need is for you to be loose in a crowd!
They used to be ordinary girls. They were hurt, bewildered, they cried, sang, danced, and put a smile on everyone's face.
I'm going to play live! I'm going to be singing! I'm going to sing!
And then it happened.
The Centernova phenomenon.
Each and every member's Keterra was born and shown.
I've never seen such light from girls who hadn't even earned their own name before.
The only member to ever pull that off was Long John.
Once was released in the afternoon, it was a月.
Our hit points result in the night too.
I'm not sure if I can't believe it, but I'm not sure if I can't believe it.
I'm not sure if I can't believe it.
Was it just a special case of beginner's walk?
I can't wipe out these vibrant feelings.
Magisa and Chieri, huh?
Do those girls have a chance of becoming this internment?
Thanks so much, everyone!
Oh, wow! What's happening?
Huh? Tsubasa-san?
I am AKB0048's manager and producer, Tsubasa Kadigiri.
Um, what's going on?
I apologize for the sudden announcement, but DGTO's anti-entertainment movement and DES attacks have been growing more intense for some time.
Therefore, I have decided that it's time for a change. One that will move us into the future.
I'm reviving the new single general elections.
Uh, no way!
General elections?
I'm also happy to announce...
What?
The return of the center nova!
Huh?
I haven't heard anything about that.
Uh-huh.
All right!
Hey, isn't that...
Yeah, that's Yugo!
You idiot!
What's happening?
Uh-huh.
Sorry for causing such a fuss, everyone.
Bye, everyone! Catch you later!
When she said general election, she meant that, right?
Yes, that appears to be the case. Fans will vote for their favorite successors and trainees, and the most popular members are selected to perform a single.
Yes, that appears to be the case.
Fans will vote for their favorite successors and trainees,
and the most popular members are selected to perform a single.
They held the elections every year when we were kids,
until Ah-Chan disappeared.
Man, why did this have to happen now?
The trainees are going to take over!
Quit freaking out.
I'm more concerned with why management decided
to bring back the center nova position.
Yeah, no kidding.
I thought they decided it was too dangerous after Ah-Chan disappeared.
Well, fighting for the center nova position has nothing to do with us.
I get the feeling we won't even be considered.
And, more importantly, the rankings.
They'll decide who's the top of the ladder and who's on the bottom.
Who's on top and who's on the bottom, huh?
Who's going to fall?
So—
If you ask me, Buddha here is as good as gone.
So konti, you!
Oh—
Come on, quit complaining.
It's time for dinner.
Oh, uh—
Uh, okay.
I can't look at it! That snapper is giving me the evil eye!
Wow, how thoughtful of them! We can all sing after dinner!
Listen up, girls! I know you're excited, but I need your attention.
Yuko?
Listen up! As of tonight, I'll be gunning for Sinternova!
Huh?
Let's all think of each other as rivals and compete as hard as we can!
You girls are my rivals too!
What is that? We're no threat! We're not nearly as talented as you are!
There's no need to act like good little trainees!
And besides, I'm not sure I'm nearly as talented as you guys give me credit for.
Sorry.
Tsubasa-san.
Huh?
What is it, Takamina?
The general elections.
They'll give Kanada a chance to become a successor, won't they?
Yes.
Oh, thank goodness!
You're worried about her.
I told you before, young souls will go through many changes as they grow, even unexpected ones.
In the end, Kanada's soul may not become like yours at all.
It may be chosen by another member.
Keep a watchful eye on Kanada,
and take care of the elections while you're at it.
I'm counting on you, Captain.
The general elections, huh?
Huh?
I was so taken aback by why Yugo said that, I didn't get the only thing!
Trust me, everyone in that room was as shocked as you are.
Yeah, I didn't think Yugo's sign would be like that.
Ah!
She's a monster!
Nagisa, you're acting real weird.
I can't believe Yugo-san considers me a rival.
It's exciting and terrifying.
But when it comes to their rankings, I don't think I'll...
No!
Uh...
Okay.
Oops.
Look out, Yuki-win!
It's the booby snatcher!
Huh?
No!
Get her!
There's not much to snatch on my UU!
Breasts are nothing more than decoration.
Up!
Get down!
Ah!
Sonata, are you okay?
My head is filled with icky!
Give her something to wear!
Please!
She's just a kid!
She could catch cold!
Hmph!
That's the least of your worries, Phil!
Ah!
What'd you say?
Don't...
Ah!
Are you okay?
That girl is Cherie's Sonow.
No!
The Zodiac Company!
Ah!
Zodiac...
What now?
As you wish, princess.
Ah!
Whoa!
This stinks!
We have received information from the WOTA.
The ship that captured Eukarin and the others is headed for Cosmogastar.
That planet is the location of the High Court, right?
Correct.
The DGTO is attempting to use special wartime laws to conduct an impromptu trial and deal a blow to our group.
By convicting members of Zero-Zero, the DGTO is trying to suppress anti-government groups rallying under AKB.
And the trial is rigged. They'll be found guilty.
Lutomiya-san, turn on the TV! You're gonna wanna see this!
In just a few moments, the public trial of three members of AKB-0048 will begin.
They were arrested under suspicion of violating the entertainment ban and participating in anti-government terror enforcement.
Public trial!
They're playing real dirty now.
Defendants, members of AKB-0048, Ioka Kuroki, Chieri Sono, and Sonata Shinanome.
The charges are thus.
The defendants resisted the DGTO in clear and willful violation of the entertainment ban.
They are also charged with planning a coup against the current government.
Hold it in. Don't react to anything.
By publicly performing illegal entertainment, AKB-0048 confused and agitated the people and disturbed the government by conducting guerrilla concerts and employing terrorist methods against the DDS.
We're not terrorists. We're just scared.
The defendants' actions robbed the people of peace and order.
Huh?
With all due respect, AKB-0048 acts out of love and compassion, not malice.
Joining with 00 was easily the proudest moment of my life.
Say what? Defendants!
Ah!
Jerry!
Infiltrating the heavily-guarded cops from a gas star is virtually impossible.
Currently, the Woda's reinforcements are assembling to organize a demonstration against the trial in the vicinity of the spaceport as a diversionary tactic.
We'll use that opportunity to strike, entering from outside the atmosphere at maximum speed using LAS.
Reckless.
It's finally time for us to take the LAS!
Quit worrying so much, alright?
You've trained for this. You're gonna be fine.
Subhasatan, look!
Defendant Chieri Sono.
Chieri.
You claim AKB-0048 acts out of love? Is that what you call your attacks on the DES?
Any injuries the DES have received were the result of self-defense.
The moment manned units appear, we are instructed to withdraw in order to avoid violence.
They are broadcasting the trial?
Yes, the signal's being broadcast all across the galaxy!
Ridiculous!
Even under wartime laws, it's illegal to broadcast a trial!
What the hell?!
Are they trying to make an example out of us?!
Correct me if I'm wrong, but you are still a trainee of these terrorists, correct?
If you admit to being deceived by AKB-0048, you can plead to extenuating circumstances.
Deceived?
Mm-hmm.
Joining AKB was my greatest dream. I sought them out myself.
They made my greatest wish come true.
And they taught me to believe in people, even complete strangers.
And those feelings grew stronger with every passing day.
If you can't trust your friends, you don't stand a chance out on that stage.
If you can't become one with them, your feelings will never reach the fans.
I don't need your extenuating circumstances.
I want to master my art in this field of dreams.
I don't want to end as a trainee.
I want to become a successor and be elected.
I want to shine as brightly as the ones before me.
I will shoot for the top and serve as a model of success for those to come.
Become the center nova.
In AKB, anything is possible.
Amazing, Thierry.
A model of success, huh?
She certainly has a way with words.
Well done, Thierry.
After that little speech, she definitely has a shot at being elected.
What are you talking about?!
She's in a dangerous situation!
Nagisa!
She's at risk!
How can you even think about the elections right now?!
At risk?
Don't be silly.
Now that we're here, she may as well be safe in bed.
There's nowhere on this planet that's dangerous now.
Thierry and the others will definitely be saved.
But how can you be so sure?
Because I'm the one who's going to rescue them!
It's like a diversionary tactic decoy entering the atmosphere.
Approaching enemy anti-air missiles.
Initiating contact.
EMP noise confirmed.
They fell for it.
Now that their radar is confused, let's get our people back.
Roger!
Ready?
It's time to show them the fruits of our labor.
It's been made perfectly clear to this court that the defendants harbor no remorse for brainwashing innocent civilians with their indecent entertainment.
My responsibility is clear.
Therefore, I order Ayako Kuroki, Chierry Sono, and Sonata Shinonome to be imprisoned for 48 standard years.
48? You're kidding!
No! That means I'll be an old lady when I get out!
About time!
Music!
Pioneer!
Alright everyone, it's show time!
Seem like there's no tomorrow!
Let's show them what we can do!
As you can see, 0048 performs extreme anti-government action, such as...
As well as our love!
Get you 00!
Is everyone alright?
Gwong!
Cheering!
Mix this!
Naraki-san!
Yugo-san!
Gwong!
Don't stop singing!
Shine on!
Gwong!
Come on, my rival.
Right!
Teyuko-san, Chieri is her rival.
But that's not all.
She's an important friend that she'll risk her life to rescue,
no matter the cost.
Risking their lives to shine as bright as stars.
Yes, just as planned.
We managed to collect data on the Carrara effect.
Furthermore, we made an extraordinary acquisition.
Due to the AKB-0048 trial,
my daughter is now,
or rather, Chieri-Sono's usefulness to us
has increased a hundredfold.
Thank you.
Ah, I'm going to ask you.
This is what I can do.
As an additional development to the revival of the General Elections, we will broadcast a television show.
This is a variety show?
This is the shine of the center nova.